Often, clients tell me they get really sore in their wrists, so I'm going to at least teach you some tricks of the trade to keep the energy focused on the forearms and out of the wrists, when you're balancing on the hands, which is what's going to happen in our next frames.
So, spreading the fingers wide, root down with the first knuckle of the first finger, and she's already doing that, as opposed to; can you show them the opposite of that, yeah, a lifted knuckle and closed fingers even.
That puts a lot of pressure in the wrist, so spread it long, and let that energy radiate out through, radiate out through the fingertips, and then press into the floor like you're pushing the floor down with the fingertips.
Now, she's got a real firm hold on the forearms.
That's a great way to do that.
The other thing is to keep the shoulder directly above the wrist, not forward from it.
When she moves the weight forward that puts a lot more stress on the wrists, so we'll come back, and all of your arm bouncing will generally have, will bend the elbow to keep this crease at a ninety degree angle, so when we come forward bending the elbow; stop right there, so you can see there's a ninety degree angle here and through the shoulder.
And then come back up, very nice.
Let's take it back; hips to heels.
That's the way to stay out of the wrists.